Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers 1966-2000 MSS 156
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Site, Cite, Sight. New York: Site, Cite, Sight, Inc. 1982.
Smith, Michael. The Big Relay Race. Chicago Books, 1981.
Smithson, Robert. Robert Smithson: Drawings. New York: The New York Cultural Center, 1974.
Smithson, Robert. The Writings of Robert Smithson: Essays with Illustrations. Ed. Nancy Holt. New York: New York University Press, 1979.
Snow, Michael. Cover to Cover. New York: New York University Press, 1975
Stevens, May. Ordinary, Extraordinary. A Summation 1977-1984. Boston: Boston University Art Gallery, 1984.
Stevens, May. Ordinary, Extraordinary. n.d.
Tellus: the audiocassette magazine. n.1, 1983.
Transmission: Theory and Practice for a new Television Aesthetics. Ed. Peter D'Agostino. New York: Tanam Press, 1985.
University of Alaska Anchorage. The Future of the book of the Future Alaska. 1994.
Unwinding the Vietnam War from War into Peace. Ed. Reese Williams. Seattle: The Real Comet Press, 1987.
Vicuña, Cecilia. Precario/Precarious. New York: Tanam Press, 1983.
Wedge. The Imperialism of Representation, the Representation of Imperialism. No. 7/8 (Winter/Spring 1985)
Weinhardt, Seth. 51 Black and White Photographs, 51 Color Drawings. New York: Chicago Books, 1985.
WhiteWalls: A Magazine of Writings by Artists. No. 5 (Winter 1981).
Williams, Reese. Clocks. 1974.
Williams, Reese. Figure-Eight, a fable. New York, Tanam Press, 1981.
Williams, Reese. A Pair of Eyes. New York: Tanam Press, 1983.
Williams, Reese. Past Trial Nearer. New York, 1978.
Winters, Robin. Consultation. n.d.
Winters, Robin. 82. 1985.
Zybert, Richard. Notebook on Time. San Francisco: Marginal Press, 1981.
ABC No Rio (New York, N.Y.).; Callard, Andrea; Collaborative Projects, Inc..; Cummington Community for the Arts, Cummington, MA.; Dickson, Jane; Geller, Matthew, 1954-; Krughoff, Fred; LINE.; O'Neill, Bonnie; Otterness, Tom, 1952-; P.S. 1 Contemporary Art Center.; Perlman, Cara;; Williams, Reese; Winters, Robin, 1950-; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities) |z New York (State) |z New York.; Art, American |z New York (State) |z New York |y 20th century.; Artists |z New York (State) |z New York.; Audiocassettes.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics) |z New York (State) |z New York |x History |y 20th century.; Correspondence.; Drawings.; Journals.; Muncie (Ind.); New York (N.Y.); Painting (image-making); Photographs.; Politics in art.; Posters.; Slides (photographs); Super 8.; Time Square Show (1980: New York, N.Y.) |v Exhibitions.; Video recordings.
- Series I: Collaborative Projects, Inc. (Colab)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains materials relating to Collaborative Projects, Inc (Colab). Andrea Callard was the Secretary of the organization from 1978-1980. Subseries A: Administrative materials includes Callard's secretarial notebook, materials relating to the group's conception, organization and functioning, grant proposals, meeting notes and announcements as well as financial information. The subseries is organized with Callard's secretarial notebook first followed by all other administrative materials in chronological order. Undated materials appear at the end of the subseries.
  - Subseries A: Administrative materials
    - Callard's secretarial notebook: Announcements. Includes information on Colab film and video projects, the Colab summer house, art opportunities and shows., ca. 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Callard's secretarial notebook: Meetings, News Notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Callard's secretarial notebook: Colab Minutes, loose., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Callard's secretarial notebook: Colab Minutes, loose., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Callard's secretarian notebok: Andrea Callard's meeting notes, loose., undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Callard's secretarial notebook: Colab Media Group, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Callard's secretarial notebook: Miscellaneous fragements, loose, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Green Corporation [early name for the organization], ca. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Money disbursement and budget, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - NEA application, Andrea Callard, Coleen Fitzgibbon and Ulli Rimius. Colab's first grant application to the NEA., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - NEA grant application supporting materials. Portfolio of member and group work., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Colab meeting announcements, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - NYSCA grant control, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Colab meeting announcements, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - NEA grant award letter, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Media Alliance, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Colab meeting announcements, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Budget, 3 March 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Funding request, Spanner/NYC, 25 April 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Letter regarding the structure and functioning of Colab. anonymous., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "Colab country house on the North Fork of Long Island, Summer 1982" AC's notation and grouping. Includes Colab Daily Purge [28 June 1982], notes, advertisements and directions. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Colab Daily Purge newsletter. 1:2 and 1:3, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Talking points re: future of Colab. unknown author., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Andrea Callard's "Colab 1984" file (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Questionnaire drafts, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Questionnaire masters, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Questionnaire responses, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cultural Council Foundation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Budget, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Meeting announcements, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Membership lists, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Mailing labels, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Colab facility, request for input from members, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Cooperative Sales Company proposal and budget, Alan Moore, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - "Shot dog incident" [AC's notation and grouping] Notes, announcements and materials relating to T. Otterness's "Shot Dog Piece.", undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Just Another Asshole call for submissions. addressed to AC [found in the box of Colab materials], undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Andrea Callard notes re: Colab. Inc. rough timeline of materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Subseries B: Colab Shows and Events
    - Doctors and Dentists Show advertisements. Org. Robin Winters. The show opened 3 February 1977 at 591 Broadway. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Note from AC to unknown recipient regarding an ambient office noise cassette used in the Doctors and Dentists show. Found in Media box 5., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Income and Wealth Show advertisements. Organized by Coleen Fitzgibbon. The show opened 3 February 1977 at 5 Bleecker St. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Press, Doctors and Dentists Show and Income and Wealth Show, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Dog Show advertisement. Opened 24 March 1977 at 591 Broadway. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Dog Show related materials, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Qwips, introductory materials such as machine use and persons involved, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Qwips, original, paper sent materials, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Qwip carbon paper received originals, part one, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Qwip carbon paper received originals, part two, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Qwip photocopies with AC annotations on reverse, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Batman show invitation. Organized by Diego Cortez. Show opened January 6 at 591 Broadway., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Colab Exhibition Project, ca. 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Manifesto Show advertisement. Organized by Jenny Holzer. 5-28 April at 5 Bleeker St., ca. 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Real Estate Show advertisements. January 1980 at 123 Delancy St. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Times Square Show advertisements. 1 June 1980- 30 June 1980 at 7th Avenue and 41st St.Includes schedule of events. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Times Square Show narrative of process and context. Unknown author., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Times Square Show invitation to private reception. 24 June 1980 at 201-205 West 41st St. at 7th Ave. (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Times Square Show, ticket to premiere screening of Matthew Geller and Judy Rifka's "True Cross Fire" on Thurs 26 June 1980. (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Times Square Show maps and layout., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Times Square Show photographs on paper., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Times Square Show slide, one image without frame, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Times Square Show press release, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Times Square Show press, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Times Square Show. Four 35mm color slides. Numbered sequentially 192-195, 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder a)
    - Times Square Show Lobby. 34 35mm color slides., 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder b)
    - Times Square Show slides from stairway in lobby., 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder c)
    - Times Square Show Money, Love and Death Room. 31 35mm color slides, 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder d)
    - Times Square Show "Willie's passage to portrait gallery". [AC's notation] 9 35mm color slides, 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder e)
    - Time's Square Show Portrait Gallery 1. 5 35mm color slides., 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder f)
    - Times Square Show Portrait Gallery 2. 25 35mm color slides., 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder g)
    - Times Square Show Fashion Lounge 2nd floor. 10 35mm color slides., 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder h)
    - Times Square Show 3rd Floor. 15 35mm color slides., 1980 (Box Binder A, Folder i)
    - Times Square Show 4th Floor. 15 35mm color slides. (Box Binder A, Folder j)
    - Brooke Alexander, Inc. Colab benefit exhibition. 6-31 December 1980 at 20 West 57th St. Announcement (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Animals Living in Cities at ABC NO RIO. Posters, exhibit program and 32 color 35mm slides., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Murder, Suicide and Show at ABC NO RIO. Six 35mm color slides taken by unknown photographer. With annotations. (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Colab Press, General, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Mural America Show, 28 March -23 April 1983, New Harmony Indiana. Announcement postcards and 21 32mm color slides. AC grouping and organization., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Colab Summer institute. 28 35mm color slides., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - "Ritz 83" AC's file on collaborative show "The Ritz" in Washington DC., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Williamsburg Bridge Sculpture show. 31 35mm color slides with annotations, two black and white contact sheets, 13 black and white snapshots., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Public Art Fund Inc. Newsletter. Spring 1983. Colab included in the listing of New York art programs. (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Announcement, Colab's A. More Store and ABC No RIO's Island of Negative Utopia drawings. 13 December 1983- 7 January 1984 at Jack Tilton Gallery., 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Colab photo postcard project "Greetings from NYC", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Announcement: A More Store at Jack Tilton Gallery and at Printed Matter., undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Proposed Amendment to New York Law re: NYSCA. [perhaps related to the Manifesto Show?] anonymous and undated. (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Series II: Andrea Callard Artist Files
  This series contains materials related to Andrea Callard's art career. The series is divided into seven subseries. Time and place figure strongly in the organization of this series because they were organizing principles in Callard's organization of her papers.
  Subseries A includes materials dated before 1973 such as items relating to her undergraduate work at San Francisco Art Institute. Subseries B reflects Callard's early years in New York city at 150 Chambers St. Artists Daisy Youngblood, Joe Haske, Robert Israel and Cara Perlman also lived in this building. Materials with specific years appear at the beginning of this subseries in chronological order. Materials designated "150 Chambers St" or "1973-1976" but without a specific date are grouped at the end of the subseries. Subseries C includes art works from Callard's first three years in her loft on the top floor of 40 Lispenard Street. Callard, Cara Perlman and Bernice Rubin secured a net lease for the top three floors of this guilding in 1976 and renovated the building. This subseries also includes work related to Callard's 1978 residency at the Cummington, Massachusetts Community for the Arts, her Ailanthus project, as well as her contributions to Colab's Dog Show and the Batman show. Subseries D includes materials relating to Callard's art career such as her contributions to the Custom and Culture II show, Colab's Animals Living in the City and the Times' Square Show as well as Callard's work with Bonnie O'Neill at Site, Cite, Sight in San Francisco. Subseries E again contains art files related to Andrea Callard's professional career including her contribution in the NYC Wildlife Museum, Inside/out garden signs at the Bronx River Art Center and Colab's Talk is Cheap street posters. Subseries F includes materials relating to Callard's art career particularly her collaboration with Sam Sue on the installation "The Tenement: Place of Survival, Object of Reform." This work appeared at the Chinatown History Project in 1988 and as part of the DIA Art Foundation "If you lived here" exhibition. Subseries G contains materials relating to Callard's art career. Most notably, the series includes work relating to her "Home Turf" window at Art in General and her storefront exhibit at Art and Architecture. The subseries also includes black and white contact sheets and negatives as well as materials relating to collaborative works during this timeperiod. Subseries H contains materials relating to Callard's work as an art teacher such as student letters, photographs and press clippings from artist in residency programs as well as teaching opportunities in New York City. Subseries I includes undated materials. Contact sheets and negatives taken by Andrea Callard compose the majority of this subseries.
  - Subseries A: 1950-1973
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder a)
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder b)
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder c)
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder d)
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder e)
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder f)
    - Color slides, 1966-1973 (Binder B, Folder g)
    - BFA diploma, San Francisco Art Institute, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Subseries B: 1973-1976, 150 Chambers St.
    - Color snapshots. Mac Becket's headshave, 150 Chambers St. Used in "Remnants of Lateral Drift", 1973 (Binder C, Folder a)
    - Rat sculpture, black and white photograph., ca. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Paper instructions to image response game. Correlates responses to their artists or author. Participants include Carol Williams, Reese Williams, Baylor Trapnell, Dede Knox, Lawrence Jacobs, Back Becket, Susan Davis, Robin Winters, Dennis Sappetelli and Bonnie O'Neill., ca. 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Image Response Game related papers., 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 91A)
    - Image response game cards and responses., ca. 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Indy 500, black and white contact sheets, photographs and negatives., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - 150 Chambers St. Activity photo performances and friends. Black and white contact sheets and photographs., 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - "Various texts 1974-77. Some relate to film and performance others are expressive, reflectiive etc. few are dated." Grouped by Andrea Callard., 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Color snapshots, documentation of umbrella sculpture, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Color snapshots and negatives. "150 Chambers St. Umbrellas shifted to tent sculpture". Used in "Remnants of Lateral Drift", 1974 (Binder C, Folder b)
    - Color snapshots and negatives. "Youngblood Haaske (at 7 years?) 150 Chambers St in Callard Hat" Images of umbrella sculpture., 1974 (Binder C, Folder c)
    - "Invisible Performances". Black and white negatives and contact sheets., ca. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - "Anonymous Person" vacuume cleaner chistening., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - "Anonymous Person" vacuum cleaner chistening., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Color contact sheet of object photographs: shoes, stones, crude hammer, six mousetraps., ca. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Mouse measurement project. color photographs, ca. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Miscellaneous drawing., ca. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Poetry by AC, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Gary Brown. black and white contact sheet and negatives, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - "Remnants of Lateral Drift", 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - "Remnants of Lateral Drift. Booklet from larger file [see folder 105 above], 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 106)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Preservation concerns include glue, acidic paper, paper in brittle plastic sleeves
    - Notes and drawings. Includes notes on past and future artworks, also photographs and contact sheets. Grouped by AC., 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Color negatives and snapshots. "Scenes of pigment drawings. Made in NYC, Telluride CO, Ogunquit ME 1975?" (Binder C, Folder d)
    - Color snapshots. Telluride CO, 1975 (Binder C, Folder e)
    - Ball State Drawing and Small Sculpture Show. AC's "Red Silk Dressing Gown (in dog bite sized Pieces)" won a prize., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Dismembered News and Comment., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - "this really is your stomach" AC color photograph of Fred Krughoff's stomach affixed to heavy cardboard with masking tape., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Color slides of A. Callard's work, watercolor, pencil., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Drawing Notebook 1975. Part I (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Drawing Notebook 1975. Part II (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Scribbling: a record of hand activity, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Henry Kissenger Multiple Choice Dictionary, ca. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Notebook. Diagrams, writing, drawings., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Notes and writing regarding AC's work, ca. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Color film stills from "Florescent Azalia", 1976 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - black and white contact sheets. images of AC doing "A Dressing Wall" work., ca. 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - "A Dressing Wall" black and white contact sheets., ca. 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - "A Dressing Wall" color photographs, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - "A Dressing Wall" color photographs on heavy cardboard., ca. 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Paper included with "A Dressing Wall" photographs on heavy cardboard, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - "A Dressing Wall" Wallet scale photographs, diagram, Tokyo subway map. grouped by AC., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Red Anger Association. Collage, Kodak advertisement and polaroid photograph. Cut out screen opens to reveal AC polaroid., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Red Anger Association. text., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - "Loft and Environs" 150 Chambers St. 69 Color slides., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Black and white negatives, contact sheets and photographs. Beatrice Rubin with dustmasks at 150 Chambers St., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Robin Winters, Baylor Trapnel in Maine., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Film shoot at a bar, invisible performances, Beatrice Rubin. Perhaps 1974., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Queen of Siberia 10 cent Cookbook. mail project, responses., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Queen of Siberia 10 cent letterhead., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Sketch notebook. Includes materials relating to "Siberia", "A Dressing Wall" and "mice" works., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Copies of drawings. Grouped in a folder by Andrea Callard., 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Color negatives and contact sheet documenting Callard's tent sculpture. Color snapsots of texture., 1973-1976 (Binder C, Folder f)
    - Color snapshots and negatives of textures and patterns., 1973-1976 (Binder C, Folder g)
    - Color snapshots and negatives. "A. Callard 150 Chambers studio. 1973-1976". Images used in "Experiences Vacuum" (Binder C, Folder h)
    - 150 Chambers Artworks. 96 color slides on six pages., 1973-1976 (Binder D, Folder a)
    - 150 Chambers Artworks. 88 color slides on seven pages., 1973-1976 (Binder D, Folder b)
    - 150 Chambers Artworks. 97 color slides on seven pages, 1973-1976 (Binder D, Folder c)
    - Artworks 1973-1975. 52 color slides on three pages. (Binder D, Folder d)
    - Artworks 1973-1975. 34 color slides on three pages. (Binder D, Folder e)
    - Artworks 1973-1975. Fourteen color slides on two pages. (Binder D, Folder f)
    - New York. 47 color slides on three pages., ca. 1973-1981 (Binder D, Folder g)
    - New York. 53 color slides on three pages., ca. 1973-1981 (Binder D, Folder h)
    - New York. 59 color slides on three pages., ca. 1973-1981 (Binder D, Folder i)
  - Subseries C: 1976-1978 40 Lispenard St.
    - "Puzzer" for Lost Shoe Blues song., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Cara Perlman on the beach., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Milkweed, windows, debris at 40 Lispenard., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. 40 Lispenard St., 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 47 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982 (Box Binder E, Folder a)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 35 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982 (Box Binder E, Folder b)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 46 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982 (Box Binder E, Folder c)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 49 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982 (Box Binder E, Folder d)
    - Canoe trip information packets AC sent to participants., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Canoe trip, black and white contact images, not entire sheets., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Canoe trip texts and Ailanthus tress. Black and white negatives and contact sheets., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Ailanthus trees, Jeff Callard and AC's grandparents, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Black and White contact sheet, partial. Ailanthus images, includes Cara Perlman at beach and one of the images used in AC's Ailanthus postcards., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Bat Pamphlet multiples. AC's contribution to Colab's Batman show. Red ink on paper, multiple., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Narrative Drawings, NEA 1976-1977. 12 color slides. (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Fred Krughoff, Cara Perlman, Alan Saret's place., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - News and Comment. Black and white photographs used, original altered newspapers and multiple copies., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Transportation incidents postcard samples., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Continental Drift at la Mama. Film by Paula Longendyke. Sets by Andrea Callard and Lizbeth Mararo. Black and white contact sheet and negatives, paper diagram, 60 color slides., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - "Love and wrongdoings and retaliation" related to Continental Drift. Index cards wtih text and black and white contact sheet images., 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Artists Space: Artists Super 8 Film Exposition. Includes Andrea Callard's Film "Standard Adult Wheelchair", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Color snapshots. "AC Hand photos. Connect to finger print drawings", 1977 (Box Binder E, Folder e)
    - Ailanthus and Cynthia 1977-1984. 36 color snapsots. (Box Binder E, Folder f)